Farah Strike Pamphlets and Broadsides 5495
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Farah Strike Pamphlets and Broadsides
1974
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Law, Gordon T., Jr.
5495
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Pamphlets, broadsides (notices).
Annual reports of the Farah Manufacturing Company, National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) materials, newspaper clippings and other printed material relating to the Amaglamated Clothing Workers of America's strike against the Farah Manufacturing Company for 18 months from 1972 to 1974.
5661380
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of annual reports of the Farah Manufacturing Company, National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) materials, newspaper clippings and other printed material relating to the Amaglamated Clothing Workers of America's strike against the Farah Manufacturing Company for 18 months from 1972 to 1974.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
R. Miles, November 19, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 14, 2019
Clothing trade -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Clothing trade -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Law, Gordon T., 1945-; Farah Manufacturing Company
5661380
- Annual reports, 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    By Farah Manufacturing Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Farah Manufacturing Company. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Broadsides, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: We Need Your Help, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). Broadside. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Attention All Working Men and Women Rally July 7, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: San Antonio Chicano Workers Will Rally July 7, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Song Sheet, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). Broadside. Item is in English;Spanish.
  - Item 5: No Work For 3 Days To Do What...Inventory!?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: I'm Glad It Was Only a Bad Dream, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Damages Sought from Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). Broadside. Copy 2. Item is in English;Spanish.
  - Item 10: Rally, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Attention All Working Men and Women Rally July 7, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). Broadside. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Attention Austin Students: Farah Workers On Strike, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Rally, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Farah Strike Calendar, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). June 27, 1973. Broadside. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Song Sheet, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: The Boss Is Taking On the Chin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Labor's Heritage, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Teachers Demonstrate Unhappiness With Nixon and Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Civil Rights Act 1964, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Why Americans Don't Want an un-American Election at Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Open Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). September 11, 1973. Broadside from the student government of the ILR School at Cornell. Item is in English
  - Item 22: Boycott Injustice, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: 3000 Strikers Need Your Help, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bulletins, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Farah Strike Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). July 30, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Strike Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). Septmeber 26, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Strike Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). no.19. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Support Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). no.2 (1973:Aug. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Support Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). no.3 (1973:Aug. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Support Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). January 14, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Support Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). January 28, 1974. Item is in English.
- Clippings, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Farah: The Strike That Has Everything, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By The Texas Observer. December 29, 1972. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Farah: The Strike That Has Everything, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By The Texas Observer. December 29, 1972. Newsclipping. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Farah: The Strike That Has Everything, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By The Texas Observer. December 29, 1972. Newsclipping. Photocopy. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Classic Labor-Organizing Drive Splits El Paso, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Homer Bigart. September 11, 1972. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Farah Largest U.S. Men's Slacks Maker, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Nancy Hamilton. October 11, 1972. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Farah, Union Attain U.S. Prominence, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Nancy Hamilton. October 10, 1972. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
- Clippings, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: High Court Rules Employer Discrimination Based Upon U.S. Citizenship Isn't Illegal, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Wall Street Journal. November 20, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Union, Farah Officials Trade Verbal Blows, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Amy Odom. September 26, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Farah Plant Layoff Involves 30 Persons, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    December 16, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Farah Announces One-Third Cut In Supervisors, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    December 15, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Report Supports Boycott of Farah Slacks, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By San Antonio Express. December 13, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Five Bishops Forced Plant Shutdowns, Farah Says, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By San Antonio News. December 13, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: "Get True Facts" Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Sharon Watkins. December 13, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Farah Wants Union Election, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By San Antonio News. July 22, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Farah, Union Exchange Hot Charges, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By San Antonio News. July 25, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Boost Given Farah Strike, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By The San Antonio Light. July 6, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Unionists Gather for Rally, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Pleas Are Made for Diginity, Justice, Fair Wages, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By David Shute. July 8, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Strikers To Get Rally Aid, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Gaylon Finklea. July 7, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: 1,000 Rally for Unionism, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Doris Wright. July 8, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Jewish Group With Strikers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By San Antonio Express. July 6, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: I Will Support the Boycott, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Joseph L. Hogan. February 14, 1973. Reprint form Courier-Jounral. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Farah Striker Responds, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By San Antonio Express. December 14, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Bishops, the Union and Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By William F. Buckley, Jr. November 6, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Farah Victim of Union Arrogance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By William Murchison. December 29, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Farah Blames Five Bishops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Nell Fenner Grover. December 13, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Farah Striker: Cool Yule for SantaWon't Wear Pants, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By The San Antonio Light. December 13, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Priest Hits Farah, Gets No Support, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Mike Hess. December 12, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Mixed S. A. Throng, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By San Antonio News. December 12, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: More Farah Protests, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By K. Mack Sisk. December 12, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Bishop Meets With Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Nell Fenner Grover. December 11, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Farah Due in S.A., Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By San Antonio Express. December 11, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Why the Union Lost Strike Against Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By San Antonio Express. August 31, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Clothing Workers Official Welcomes Press Conference, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By The El Paso Times. January 26, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Farah Employes Reject Union With a 71-32 Vote, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By The El Paso Times. January 27, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Farah Jean Boycott Hits Ithaca, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Kathy Levine. September 21, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Farah Strike: Archbishop Firm, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Nell Fenner Grover. December 14, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: What About the Farah Workers?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Daniel Lyons. December 7, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Bishops Meet: Hits, Runs, Errors, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Daniel Lyons. December 14, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Bishop Metzger vs. Dr. Poling, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Daniel Lyons. December 9, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: The Farah Dispute, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Daniel Lyons. November 11, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: A Boycott Begins to Hurt at Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Business Week. June 2, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Strikes: A Bishop v. Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Time. March 26, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Farah Strike Has Become War of Attrition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Philip Shabecoff. June 10, 1973. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
- Clippings, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Tough Bargaining Before Farah Reopens, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By San Antonio News. February 25, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Picketing, Not Boycott, Proved Farah's Downfall, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Fritz Wirt. March 25, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Some Reluctant to Talk: Benefits, Wages Increase is Hope, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Steven Peters. February 26, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: 186,300 Shares of Farah Traded on Stock Market, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    February 26, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: This Farah Thing' Escalated From Plant to Moral Battle, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Allen Pusey. January 8, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Farah Urges Plant-Wide Election: Spokesman Claims Union Will Stall, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Steve Hallock. January 8, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Farah, ACWA Pact Reached Prior to Union Recognition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Fritz Wirt. March 24, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Farah Employes Vote Today On Acceptance of Pact Agreement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    March 7, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Farah Workers OK Three-Year Pact, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    March 8, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Contract Talks Set Next Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    February 25, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Four Years, Three Months and 26 Confusing Days Later, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    February 24, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Settlement Will Pave Way To Reopen Plants, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Farah Settlement Near, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    February 23, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Point, Counter-Point Continues, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    February 6, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Farah-ACWA Battle Thickens, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By The El Paso Times. January 22, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: NLRB Hearing Officer Dismisses Move to Halt Anti-Farah Picket, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    January 10, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Tower Urges Elections At Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By John E. Simonds. January 17, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: An In-Depth Study of the Farah Dispute That Lingers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Steven R. Reed; K. Mack Sisk. January 7, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Goals, Hopes and Dreams Change for Picketers After Two Years, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: To Unionize Or Not... Council Probes Question, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: Meany Cites Benefits in Farah Victory, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Philip Shabecoff. February 26, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Farah Ordered to Rehire Striking Workers In Broad Preliminary Report by NLRB Aide, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Wall Street Journal. January 29, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Ruling on Farah Union Is the Latest Step in a Clash of Two Cultures, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Martin Waldron. February 4, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: A Texas Pants Maker Loses to a Boycott, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Business Week. March 2, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Farah Knuckles Under, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Time. March, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Tragedy in Texas, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Daniel Lyons. January 6, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: N.L.R.B. Aide Orders Farah Penalties, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Philip Shabecoff. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Buy Farah Slacks, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By The San Antonio Light. February 26, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Farah Talks Forecast This Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By San Antonio Express. February 26, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Farah Accord Hailed, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By The San Antonio Light. February 25, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Farah Vows to Continue Struggle Against Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Frank Del Olmo; Harry Bernstein. February 2, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Farah Plants End a 21 Month Strike, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Emanuel Perlmutter. February 25, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Farah's Strike Is Over, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By San Antonio Express. February 25, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Southwest Push Planned By Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 35: $440 Cash, and Some Sleep, Too, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 36: Farah Slack Factories; Concentration Camps?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By K. Mack Sisk; Steven R. Reed. January 31, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: A Powerful Weapon, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Daniel Lyons. January 18, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: "According to a compliation released not long ago... ", Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Beth Bogie. August, 1974. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Farah Recognizes Clothing Workers As Union Agent, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Wall Street Jounral. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
- Clippings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  undated
  - Item 1: Farah Pants Boycott Headed for the College Campus, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Don't Buy Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By The Cornell Daily Sun. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Back to the Thirties, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Meany Cites Gain in Farah Victory, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Distinguished Americans Who Support Farah Strikers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Jewish Group With Strikers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Jewish Organizations in 2 Cities Add Their Support to the Boycott, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Jewish Groups Back Farah Action, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Israel Labor Gives Contribution to Help Striking Farah Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Bishop of El Paso Renews His Appeal for Support of the Farah Strikers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By S. M. Metzger. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Union Playing for Big Stakes at El Paso Plant, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Mike Cochran. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Protest Signs Lay Under Tree As 30 Workers React to Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Ron Dusek. Newsclipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 13:... As Result Of Picketing, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- District Court of El Paso County, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Farah vs. ACWA, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By District Court of El Paso County, Texas. August 1, 1972. no. 72-2045. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Farah vs. ACWA, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By District Court of Bexar County, Texas. June 25, 1973. Item is in English.
- William F. Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: William F. Farah: Man of the Year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Alan R. Walden. Reprinted from Clothes, v.8:no.19 (1973:Dec. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: William F. Farah: Man of the Year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Alan R. Walden. Reprinted from Clothes, v.8:no.19 (1973:Dec. 15). Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: To: Student Committees to Aid the Farah Strikers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Murray H. Finley; Jacob Sheinkman. November 3, 1973. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Farah Repeats Offer For Union Elections, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Farah Manufacturing Company. July 22, 1973. Press Release. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Commentaries, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Joint Statement by Representatives of Farah Manufacturing Company and the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America); Farah Manufacturing Company. March 7, 1974. Press Release. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Resolution of the Student Government of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Student Government of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Dear Mr. Gordon Law, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Gordon W. Foster. April 5, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Dear Customer, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By William F. Farah. November 5, 1973. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Dear Mr. Louis V. Baldovin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By William F. Farah. July 20, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Farah Manufacturing Company, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Sales and Profits. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Student Farah Committees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Statement On Behalf of Women's Groups: Rally For Dignity and Decent Wages, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    July 2, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Background Sheet for Press Conference of Women's Group, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Brand Label sheet, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Dear Fellow Priest, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Francis J. Furey. June 28, 1973. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Statement of Support, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    December 12, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Farah Manufacturing Company, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Fact sheet. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Latest Developments on the Farah Boycott, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Dear Brothers and Sisters, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Joe J. Bernal. June 29, 1973. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Press Release, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    February 7, 1974. Item is in English.
- National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Petition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Kenneth R. Carr. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Complaint and Notice of Hearing, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Arthur Safos. April 19, 1973. Case no. 23-CB-1331. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Complaint, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Louis V. Baldovin. June 28, 1973. Case no. 23-CP-78. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Order Consolidating Cases, Amended Consolidated Complaint, and Notice of Hearing, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By James W. Mast. July 6, 1973. Case nos. 28-CB-701; 28-CB-733; 28-CB-757. Item is in English.